Guide to the Harris Masterson I papers,1860-1942, bulk 1880-1920 MS 468
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Legal Papers by County (Boxes 190-262)
  - Subseries A: Legal/Land
    - Harris County
      - J. Austin G. Gostieta (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - D. Alexander (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - J. Austin Irvin Place (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - J. Austin Hollingsworth Survey (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - J. Austin (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - J. Austin, Germantown Suddv, Schwartz Tract (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - J. Austin Sessums Property (Box 209, Folder 11)
      - J. Austin Ryon 26 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - M. Baker, J. C. Christy, J. S. Holman (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - M. Baker J. S. Holman (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - J. Beldin (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - G. Bellows (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - J. S. Black (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - J. H. Callahan (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - J. S. Collins Belt Junction City (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - W. Colton (Box 210, Folder 9)
      - M. DeYoung W. J. Lovett Survey (Box 210, Folder 10)
      - G. Galbraith (Box 210, Folder 11)
      - A. Goldman (Box 210, Folder 12)
      - O. Hacker (Box 210, Folder 13)
      - E. P. Hage (Box 210, Folder 14)
      - W. D. C. Hall (Box 210, Folder 15)
      - J. T. Harrel (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - D. Harris (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - D. Harris Clear Cr. (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - D. Harris (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - D. W. C. Harris (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - D. W. C. Harris ¼ League (Box 211, Folder 6)
      - D. W. C. Harris ¼ League (Box 211, Folder 7)
      - J. R. Harris Mamie McFarland (Box 211, Folder 8)
      - S. M. Harris Ellis Benson (Box 211, Folder 9)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 211, Folder 10)
      - S. M. Harris J. D. Staples (Box 211, Folder 11)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 211, Folder 12)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 211, Folder 13)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - S. M. Harris (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - W. P. Harris (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - W. P. Harris (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - W. P. Harris Wilson (Box 212, Folder 6)
      - W. P. Harris (Box 212, Folder 7)
      - S. O. Hawkins (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - W. Hedge, A. J. Holder, W. H. Steel (Box 212, Folder 9)
      - W. Hironymus (Box 212, Folder 10)
      - J. S. Harris Lot 15 (Box 212, Folder 11)
      - J. S. Harris Lot 7 (Box 212, Folder 12)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 2 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 6 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 14 (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 27 (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 39 (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 46 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - J. S. Holman Lot 68, 87, 58 (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - H. T. C. Railroad Co. #7 Great Northern Addition (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - H. T. C. Railroad Co. #64 Block 2 (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - H. T. B. Railroad Co. Jacob Bates (Box 213, Folder 10)
      - H. T. B. Railroad Co. #2 (Box 213, Folder 11)
      - H. T. B. Railroad Co. #3 (Box 213, Folder 12)
      - H. T. B. Railroad Co. #4 (Box 213, Folder 13)
      - H. T. B. Railroad Co. #11 13, Dairy Prod. (Box 213, Folder 14)
      - J. B. Jones (Box 213, Folder 15)
      - J. Karcher, S. Everett, N. Brady (Box 213, Folder 16)
      - W. Latham J. H. Callahan (Box 213, Folder 17)
      - A. Lawson (Box 213, Folder 18)
      - H. K. Lewis (Box 213, Folder 19)
      - N. Lynch (Box 213, Folder 20)
      - A. McCormick (Box 213, Folder 21)
      - W. McWilkinson (Box 214, Folder 1)
      - J. Merry (Box 214, Folder 2)
      - J. C. Megginson (Box 214, Folder 3)
      - L. Moore (Box 214, Folder 4)
      - L. Moore J. Thomas (Box 214, Folder 5)
      - M. Moran (Box 214, Folder 6)
      - K. Morris (Box 214, Folder 7)
      - K. Morris (Box 214, Folder 8)
      - J. O'Brien (Box 214, Folder 9)
      - B. Page (Box 214, Folder 10)
      - G. M. Patrick (Box 214, Folder 11)
      - P. Reels J. Trobaugh (Box 214, Folder 12)
      - J. Reinerman Dupree Tract (Box 214, Folder 13)
      - A. C. Reynolds (Box 214, Folder 14)
      - P. W. Rose (Box 214, Folder 15)
      - W. Scott (Box 214, Folder 16)
      - A. Smith Little York Survey (Box 214, Folder 17)
      - A. Smith (Box 214, Folder 18)
      - O. Smith Fitze Homestead (Box 214, Folder 19)
      - O. Smith Hadley Home Reserve (Box 214, Folder 20)
      - O. Smith (Box 214, Folder 21)
      - O. Smith Johnson 10 acres (Box 215, Folder 1)
      - O. Smith (Box 215, Folder 2)
      - T. J. Stansbury (Box 215, Folder 3)
      - J. Strange Eckols Tract (Box 215, Folder 4)
      - P. Sullivan (Box 215, Folder 5)
      - W. W. Swain (Box 215, Folder 6)
      - T. Toby (Box 215, Folder 7)
      - N. W. Travis (Box 215, Folder 8)
      - WCRR #2 M. A. Preston (Box 215, Folder 9)
      - WCRR #4 M. A. Preston (Box 215, Folder 10)
      - WCRR #6 M. A. Preston (Box 215, Folder 11)
      - N. B. Waters Almeda, town of (Box 215, Folder 12)
      - J. Waugh (Box 215, Folder 13)
      - J. White (Box 215, Folder 14)
      - H. Whiting (Box 215, Folder 15)
      - W. Whitlock (Box 215, Folder 16)
      - C. Williams H. K. Lewis (Box 215, Folder 17)
      - S. M. Williams (Box 215, Folder 18)
      - S. M. Williams J. R. Harris (Box 216, Folder 1)
      - S. M. Williams J. R. Harris (Box 216, Folder 2)
      - J. Strange (Box 216, Folder 3)
      - J. Strange (Box 216, Folder 4)
      - S. S. B. B. Dissen. Heights (Box 216, Folder 5)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 14 (Box 216, Folder 6)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 14 (Box 216, Folder 7)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 28 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 1)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 49 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 2)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 51 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 3)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 51 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 4)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 56 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 5)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 56 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 6)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 72 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 7)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 73 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 8)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 80 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 9)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 80 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 10)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 83 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 217, Folder 11)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 84 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 1)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 93 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 2)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 95 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 3)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 96 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 4)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 97 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 5)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 98 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 6)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 99 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 7)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 129 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 8)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 135 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 9)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 159 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 10)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 246 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 11)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 256 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 12)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 287 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 13)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 295 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 14)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 331 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 15)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 345 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 16)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 362 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 17)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 389 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 18)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 402 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 19)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 419 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 20)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 420 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 21)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 434 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 22)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 434 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 23)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 480 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 24)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 497 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 25)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 510 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 26)
      - S. S. B. B. Block 576 (South Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 218, Folder 27)
      - N. S. B. B. Block 3-4 (North Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 219, Folder 1)
      - N. S. B. B. Block 284 (North Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 219, Folder 2)
      - N. S. B. B. Block 369-370 (North Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 219, Folder 3)
      - Houston, City of: C. M. Allen Add. Block 40 (Box 219, Folder 4)
      - Houston, City of: C. M. Allen Add. Block 43 (Box 219, Folder 5)
      - Houston, City of: A. C. Allen Add. Block 30 (Box 219, Folder 6)
      - Houston, City of: A. C. Allen Add. Block 49 (Box 219, Folder 7)
      - Houston, City of: A. C. Allen Add. Block "B" (Box 219, Folder 8)
      - Houston, City of: A. C. Allen Add. Block 4 (Box 219, Folder 9)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. (Box 219, Folder 10)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. (Box 219, Folder 11)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 56 (Box 219, Folder 12)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 61 (Box 219, Folder 13)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 69 (Box 219, Folder 14)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 83 (Box 219, Folder 15)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 258 (Box 219, Folder 16)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 284 (Box 219, Folder 17)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 291 (Box 219, Folder 18)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 299 (Box 219, Folder 19)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 385, J. Austin estate (Box 219, Folder 20)
      - Houston, City of: W. R. Baker Add. Block 470 (Box 219, Folder 21)
      - Houston, City of: Barnes Westmore Add. Block B (Box 219, Folder 22)
      - Houston, City of: Barnes Westmore Add. Block D (Box 219, Folder 23)
      - Houston, City of: J. Brashear Add. Block 2 11 (Box 219, Folder 24)
      - Houston, City of: Bruner Add. Block 26, 82, 84, 88, 106 (Box 219, Folder 25)
      - Houston, City of: Bruner Add. Block 29 (Box 219, Folder 26)
      - Houston, City of: J. Bute Add. Block 9 (Box 219, Folder 27)
      - Houston, City of: J. Bute Add. Block 10 (Box 219, Folder 28)
      - Houston, City of: Cascara Add. Block 6 (Box 220, Folder 1)
      - Houston, City of: Cascara Add. Block 6 (Box 220, Folder 2)
      - Houston, City of: Cascara Add. Block 11 (Box 220, Folder 3)
      - Houston, City of: Cascara Add. Block 21 (Box 220, Folder 4)
      - Houston, City of: Castina Add. Block 22 (Box 220, Folder 5)
      - Houston, City of: Castina Add. Block 27 (Box 220, Folder 6)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman Add. (Box 220, Folder 7)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman 2nd Add. Block 3 (Box 220, Folder 8)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman 2nd Add. Block 14 (Box 220, Folder 9)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman 2nd Add. Block 22 (Box 220, Folder 10)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman 2nd Add. Block 22 (Box 220, Folder 11)
      - Houston, City of: Chapman 3rd Add. Block 43 (Box 220, Folder 12)
      - Houston, City of: Collins Add. Block 41 115 (Box 220, Folder 13)
      - Houston, City of: Davis Add. Block D (Box 220, Folder 14)
      - Houston, City of: Denver Add. (Box 220, Folder 15)
      - Houston, City of: Driscoll Add. (Box 220, Folder 16)
      - Houston, City of: Eagle Add. Block 9 (Box 220, Folder 17)
      - Houston, City of: Emancipation Park (Box 220, Folder 18)
      - Houston, City of: Fairground Add. Block 7, Block 2-4 (3rd Add.) (Box 221, Folder 1)
      - Houston, City of: Fairground Add. Block 29 (Box 221, Folder 2)
      - Houston, City of: Fairground Add. Block 46 (Box 221, Folder 3)
      - Houston, City of: Fairground 2nd Add. Block 1 (Box 221, Folder 4)
      - Houston, City of: J. E. Foster Subov. Block 2 Harley Add. Block 1-2 (Box 221, Folder 5)
      - Germantown (Box 221, Folder 6)
      - Houston, City of: Gregg. Add. Block 2 J. S. Black Chapman 2nd Add. Block 3 (Box 221, Folder 7)
      - Houston, City of: Hadley Franklin (Box 221, Folder 8)
      - Houston, City of: Hardcastle Add. Block 27 (Box 221, Folder 9)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Railroad Co. Add. Block 4 (Box 221, Folder 10)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Railroad Co. Add. 4 Block 8 (Box 221, Folder 11)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Harbor Add. (Box 221, Folder 12)
      - Houston, City of: Kenilworth Grove Add. (Box 221, Folder 13)
      - Houston, City of: Little or Dickenson Add. Block 27 (Box 221, Folder 14)
      - Houston, City of: Lockhart-Conner-Brazoria Add. Block 16 (Box 221, Folder 15)
      - Houston, City of: McGowan Add. (Box 221, Folder 16)
      - Houston, City of: MacGregor-Bludgett Add. (Box 221, Folder 17)
      - Houston, City of: MacGregor-Bludgett Add. (Box 221, Folder 18)
      - Houston, City of: Main St. Add. Block 6 (Box 221, Folder 19)
      - Houston, City of: Michau Add. Block 13 (Box 221, Folder 20)
      - Houston, City of: Montrose Add. Block 8 (Box 221, Folder 21)
      - Houston, City of: Montrose Add. Block 58 (Box 221, Folder 22)
      - Houston, City of: Noble Add. (Box 221, Folder 23)
      - Houston, City of: Perry Block (Box 222, Folder 1)
      - Houston, City of: Ranger Add. Block 549 (Box 222, Folder 2)
      - Houston, City of: Ranger Add. Block 604 (Box 222, Folder 3)
      - Houston, City of: Ranger Add. Block 604 (Box 222, Folder 4)
      - N. S. B. B. Riverside Block 10 (North Side Buffalo Bayou) (Box 222, Folder 5)
      - Houston, City of: Ryon Add. Block 130 Burnett Add. Block 3 (Box 222, Folder 6)
      - Houston, City of: Settegast Udham Add. Block 17 (Box 222, Folder 7)
      - Houston, City of: Parker Smith Add. Block 15 (Box 222, Folder 8)
      - South End Villa Tract (Box 222, Folder 9)
      - South End Villa Tract (Box 222, Folder 10)
      - Houston, City of: L. B. Sweeney Add., Syndor Add., Barnes Westmore Add., Main St. Add. (Box 222, Folder 11)
      - Houston, City of: Sydnor Add. Block 2 (Box 222, Folder 12)
      - Houston, City of: Sydnore Add. Block 3 (Box 222, Folder 13)
      - Houston, City of: Sydnore Add. Block 3 (Box 222, Folder 14)
      - Houston, City of: Texas Savings Real Estate Add. Block 1 J. S. Holman Block 21 (Box 222, Folder 15)
      - Houston, City of: Tierwester Add. Block 3 (Box 223, Folder 1)
      - Houston, City of: Walker Survey, Frazier (Box 223, Folder 2)
      - Houston, City of: W. B. Walker Add. Block 10 (Box 223, Folder 3)
      - Houston, City of: West End Add. (Box 223, Folder 4)
      - Houston, City of: West End. Add (Box 223, Folder 5)
      - Houston, City of: Westmoreland Add. Block 5 (Box 223, Folder 6)
      - Houston, City of: Westmoreland Add. Block 9 (Box 223, Folder 7)
      - Houston, City of: Westmoreland Add. Block 9 (Box 223, Folder 8)
      - Houston, City of: Westmoreland Add. Block 9 (Box 223, Folder 9)
      - Houston, City of: Westmoreland Add. Block 10 (Box 223, Folder 10)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Heights Block 9 (Box 223, Folder 11)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Heights Block 151 (Box 223, Folder 12)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Heights Block 186 (Box 223, Folder 13)
      - Houston, City of: Houston Heights Block 300 (Box 223, Folder 14)
      - Brunsville, Town of (Box 223, Folder 15)
      - Deepwater, Town of (Box 223, Folder 16)
      - Deepwater, Town of: Block 20 (Box 223, Folder 17)
      - Hockley, Town of: Block 12 (Box 223, Folder 18)
      - Pasadena, Town of: Block 71 (Box 223, Folder 19)
      - LaPorte, Town of: Beach Park Annex (Box 223, Folder 20)
      - LaPorte, Town of: Block 293 (Box 223, Folder 21)
      - S. Houston, Town of (Box 223, Folder 22)
      - Webster, Town of: Block 19 (Box 223, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 224, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous 1 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous 2 (Box 224, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous 3 (Box 224, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous 4 (Box 224, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous 5 (Box 224, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 225, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous 1 (Box 225, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous 2 (Box 225, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous 3 (Box 225, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous 4 (Box 225, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous 5 (Box 225, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous 6 (Box 226, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous 7 (Box 226, Folder 2)
      - Title abstract related (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Henderson County
      - Isaac Greeson (Box 226, Folder 5)
      - J. S. Johnston (Box 226, Folder 4)
      - J. Y. Perez (Box 226, Folder 6)
      - D. O. Williams (Box 226, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 226, Folder 8)
    - Hidalgo County
      - Title abstract related (Box 227, Folder 1)
      - Santo Tomas De Le Blanca Tract (Box 227, Folder 2)
      - T. C. Baird v. Masterson, Atkinson, Masterson (Box 227, Folder 3)
      - J. J. Ball San Salvador Del Tule Grant (Box 227, Folder 4)
      - San Salvador Del Tule Grant (Box 227, Folder 5)
      - Hill County: Mo-Pacific Railroad (Box 227, Folder 6)
      - Houston County: Title abstract related (Box 227, Folder 7)
      - Houston County: Patton family (Box 227, Folder 8)
      - Jackson Matagorda Counties (Box 227, Folder 9)
      - Jackson County: Ramon Musquiz (Box 227, Folder 10)
    - Jasper County
      - J. L. Williams Masterson, Atkinson, Masterson (Box 227, Folder 11)
      - Title abstract related (Box 227, Folder 12)
      - C. A. Felder (Box 227, Folder 13)
      - Elijah Isaacs (Box 227, Folder 14)
      - Jefferson Laird (Box 227, Folder 15)
      - T. McGallion (Box 227, Folder 16)
      - J. Milhome (Box 227, Folder 17)
      - T. Tanner (Box 227, Folder 18)
      - Enrique Webb (Box 228, Folder 1)
      - T. N. O. Railroad Co. (Box 228, Folder 2)
      - William Wilson P. B. Pry (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - Jefferson County
      - Title abstract related (Box 228, Folder 4)
      - Title abstract related (Box 228, Folder 5)
      - W. B. Burton League (Box 228, Folder 6)
      - William Carr (Box 228, Folder 7)
      - E. D. Chenneth (Box 228, Folder 8)
      - Mrs. P. B. Chiles (Box 228, Folder 9)
      - Beamount, City of: Block 38, Lot 177 (Box 229, Folder 1)
      - Beamount, City of: Block 38, Lot 177 (Box 229, Folder 2)
      - Beamount, City of: Block 38, Lot 177 (Box 229, Folder 3)
      - D. A. Cunningham (Box 229, Folder 4)
      - P. Humphries (Box 229, Folder 5)
      - J. Kirby (Box 229, Folder 6)
      - William McFarland (Box 229, Folder 7)
      - Stivers (Box 229, Folder 8)
      - A. V. Sancier (Box 229, Folder 9)
      - W. N. Sigler (Box 229, Folder 10)
      - T. N. O. Railroad Co., section 30 (Box 229, Folder 11)
      - J. A. Veatch Spindletop Heights (Box 229, Folder 12)
      - J. A. Veatch Spindletop Heights (Box 229, Folder 13)
    - Jefferson Liberty Counties: A. B. Barrier (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Jefferson Hardin Counties: N. F. Chambers (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Jefferson County: Miscellaneous (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Johnson County: P. Morton (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Johnson Hood Counties: G. B. Jameson (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - Jones County: T. B. Stephens (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - LaSalle County: Title abstract related (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - Leon County: Title abstract related (Box 230, Folder 8)
    - Leon County: Title abstract related (Box 230, Folder 9)
    - Leon County: Jones Masterson (Box 230, Folder 10)
    - Leon County: R. Reins William Mann (Box 230, Folder 11)
    - Leon Robertson Counties (Box 230, Folder 12)
    - Liberty County
      - Title abstract related (Box 230, Folder 13)
      - J. Blair (Box 230, Folder 14)
      - P. Blanchett (Box 230, Folder 15)
      - William Bloodgood (Box 230, Folder 16)
      - M. Buye (Box 230, Folder 17)
      - M. Buye (Box 230, Folder 18)
      - M. Buye (Box 230, Folder 19)
      - M. Buye (Box 231, Folder 1)
      - A. M. De La Jarza (Box 231, Folder 2)
      - Jose Delgado (Box 231, Folder 3)
      - C. Dorsett (Box 231, Folder 4)
      - J. Doswell (Box 231, Folder 5)
      - J. Dunman (Box 231, Folder 6)
      - L. Gedruf (Box 231, Folder 7)
      - F. Gibenrath (Box 231, Folder 8)
      - A. Green (Box 231, Folder 9)
      - B. W. Hardin (Box 231, Folder 10)
      - M. A. Hardin (Box 231, Folder 11)
      - C. Harper (Box 231, Folder 12)
      - I. Junker (Box 231, Folder 13)
      - J. Malley (Box 231, Folder 14)
      - J. Martin (Box 231, Folder 15)
      - J. D. Martinez (Box 231, Folder 16)
      - J. E. Mayfield (Box 231, Folder 17)
      - P. Miller (Box 231, Folder 18)
      - F. Millon (Box 231, Folder 19)
      - E. Munson (Box 231, Folder 20)
      - M. Smith (Box 231, Folder 21)
      - E. M. Tanner (Box 231, Folder 22)
      - M. Whittington (Box 231, Folder 23)
      - J. Young (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Liberty Harris Counties: L. Latham (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Limestone County (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Limestone County: W. P. Baxter (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Llano County: Title abstract related (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Llano County: Lane, Masterson Opp. (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Llano County: J. Simon (Box 232, Folder 8)
    - Madison County: Title abstract related (Box 232, Folder 9)
    - Marion County: Title abstract related (Box 232, Folder 10)
    - Matagorda County
      - J. Giboney Masterson (Box 232, Folder 11)
      - Title abstract related (Box 232, Folder 12)
      - H. H. League (Box 232, Folder 13)
      - "G" Pasture (Box 232, Folder 14)
      - "G" Pasture (Box 232, Folder 15)
      - Oil land (Box 232, Folder 16)
    - Maverick County (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Maverick Kinney Counties (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - McCulloch County (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - McLennan County: Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - McLennon County (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - McMullen County: Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Medina County: Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Menard County: Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Milam County: Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Milam County: J. H. I. Muldrow (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Milam County: William Robertson (Box 233, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery County
      - Title abstract related (Box 233, Folder 12)
      - J. Crouch (Box 233, Folder 13)
      - L. Flatlaw (Box 233, Folder 14)
      - M. R. Goheen (Box 233, Folder 15)
      - McDermitt (Box 233, Folder 16)
      - N. Martin (Box 233, Folder 17)
      - T. J. Nichols (Box 233, Folder 18)
      - J. Owens (Box 233, Folder 19)
      - J. C. Pitts (Box 233, Folder 20)
      - B. Pruett (Box 233, Folder 21)
      - S. Ward (Box 233, Folder 22)
      - Washington Co. Railroad Co. Survey (Box 233, Folder 23)
      - Frank H. Boye (Box 234, Folder 1)
      - W. Wills (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Nacogdoches County
      - Title abstract related (Box 234, Folder 3)
      - Jose De Los Santos Coy Grant Juana Maria Sierra Grant (Box 234, Folder 4)
      - Jose De Los Campos Coy Grant Juana Maria Sierra Grant (Box 234, Folder 5)
      - J. Flores (Box 234, Folder 6)
      - J. Holloway (Box 234, Folder 7)
      - R. A. Lewis (Box 235, Folder 1)
      - M. L. McClave (Box 235, Folder 2)
      - J. M. Mora Santos Coy (Box 235, Folder 3)
      - R. Nelson (Box 235, Folder 4)
      - M. Roberts (Box 235, Folder 5)
      - W. Robinson (Box 235, Folder 6)
      - J. M. Sierra J. Cordova (Box 235, Folder 7)
      - B. Testard (Box 235, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 235, Folder 9)
      - J. H. Bowman (Box 235, Folder 10)
      - J. A. Chireno (Box 235, Folder 11)
    - Navarro County: T. Smith (Box 235, Folder 12)